{
"question": "貴方-1",
"answer": "あなた"
},
{
"question": "欲しい",
"answer": "ほしい"
},
{
"question": "行く",
"answer": "いく"
},
{
"question": "乗る",
"answer": "のる"
},
{
"question": "大きな",
"answer": "おおきな"
},
{
"question": "医者",
"answer": "いしゃ"
},
{
"question": "終わる",
"answer": "おわる"
},
{
"question": "学生",
"answer": "がくせい"
},
{
"question": "長い",
"answer": "ながい"
},
{
"question": "何の",
"answer": "どの"
},
{
"question": "国",
"answer": "くに"
},
{
"question": "又",
"answer": "また"
},
{
"question": "高い",
"answer": "たかい"
},
{
"question": "余り",
"answer": "あまり"
},
{
"question": "難しい",
"answer": "むずかしい"
},
{
"question": "友達",
"answer": "ともだち"
},
{
"question": "本当",
"answer": "ほんとう"
},
{
"question": "一つ",
"answer": "ひとつ"
},
{
"question": "寝る",
"answer": "ねる"
},
{
"question": "生徒",
"answer": "せいと"
},
